knowinservers.com 2011-09-27

# Privacy Policy : Knowin Servers

This Privacy Policy discusses how knowinservers.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from our customers, visitors to our websites, individuals who contact us and visitors to our customers websites (all: Users).  
Please review our Privacy Policy in conjunction with our Acceptable Use Policy (AUP) and your contract with us. The terms of this Privacy Policy are in addition to the terms of our AUP and our contract. We collect information from Users in many ways. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide Users with an understanding of what types of information we collect, how we treat it, and choices they may have related to this information. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. To stay updated on our current Privacy Policy, please visit this page often. If you have a question about how a certain type of information is handled, please e-mail us at: support@knowinservers.com.

Information that we collect  
Customer Record When Users become customers they provide us with their address, email, phone number, and credit card. Users may also provide us with their fax number and company affiliation (together Customer Record).

Inquiries When Users contact us we may ask for information that allows us to contact them, validate the seriousness of their inquiry and request specific information related to the reason they have contacted us (User Inquiry Information).

Statistical Information All of our servers collect statistical information such as Users IP addresses, dates Users visit, computers Users are using, and operating system, among other data (Statistical Information).

Cookies Our website uses cookies. These data files are read by our server to determine whether Users have visited our site before, how often, the length of time and which pages Users view. The equipment we use to provide Services to Users may also place cookies on their computers.

How we use information that we collect.  
knowinservers.com is required to comply with demands for information as dictated by State and Federal law. Examples of these demands include subpoenas, warrants, and civil discovery demands. Information covered by our Privacy Policy may be disclosed following such a request if we determine, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure is necessary or required. We may also disclose this information if it is necessary or required to protect our interests, the interests of our customers, or in connection with the sale of our business.

Customer Record We use the Customer Record to identify Users personally. It is used throughout our business to provide services to Users. Information in your Customer Record will only be shared with third parties if it is necessary to provide Third Party products to you. However, information in the Customer Record related to payments, such as a Users credit card number, is only used to ensure we receive payment for services rendered.

Customer Inquiries We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify Users personally. It is used throughout our business to provide services to  
Users. Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties in the following circumstances: to identify and fix problems with services we provide when we are not capable of doing so ourselves.

Statistical Information We do not use Statistical Information to identify Users personally. We use statistical information to operate our hardware and software, diagnose problems and administer our website. We may use aggregate information to modify the products and services we offer based on who is visiting our website, and what they are purchasing.

Cookies We may use Cookies to identify Users personally. We use the information provided by cookies to change the way our website looks to Users; to keep Users logged in to certain areas of the website; to ensure continued connection to the Equipment; and to collect demographic data about where Users go on our website and how they behave. Cookies used by our Equipment are used to track and log activities on the Equipment and our Network for security, network maintenance and other related activities.

Tracking Software We do not use Tracking Software to identify Users personally. We use the information provided by Tracking Software to determine the effectiveness of our marketing programs; improve the functionality of our website; and to collect demographic data about where Users go on our website and how they behave.

Data Retention and Security  
We keep the information covered by this Privacy Policy indefinitely. Information collected from our website is protected by SSL 128 bit encryption technology during transmission. Information kept by us in our business is protected using industry standard security measures. Our employees are required to keep information covered by this Privacy Policy confidential unless disclosure is authorized in this Privacy Policy, or by Users. No means of communication or information transmission or storage is totally secure. Because of this we are not responsible for loss corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of information covered by this Privacy Policy, or for any resulting damages, including unauthorized acquisition and use.
